<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>BLOG – Ayoub AIT ELMOKHTAR</title>
    <link>https://ayoubmokhtar.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on BLOG – Ayoub AIT ELMOKHTAR</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:21:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ayoubmokhtar.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How OSCP could reveal the real you.</title>
      <link>https://ayoubmokhtar.com/post/how-oscp-could-reveal-the-real-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 17:21:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ayoubmokhtar.com/post/how-oscp-could-reveal-the-real-you/</guid>
      <description>Brief overview: Fear, disappointment, failure with many other bad things have been experienced by most of OSCP holders, It’s not a shame to admit it and if you ask people around regarding its difficulty, you will get various types of answers with one signification. OSCP is the toughest exam they&amp;rsquo;ve taken in their lives. Offensive Security Certified Professional. one of the most well-recognized and respected certifications in the security industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[PayPal BBP] I Could’ve Deleted All SMC Messages. Using Brute Force Technique.</title>
      <link>https://ayoubmokhtar.com/post/paypal-bbp-i-couldve-deleted-all-smc-messages-using-brute-force-technique/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Apr 2019 23:40:46 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ayoubmokhtar.com/post/paypal-bbp-i-couldve-deleted-all-smc-messages-using-brute-force-technique/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: While playing around with SMC platform at paypal.com, I came across an interesting endpoint which doesn’t include CSRF token within its request when you delete a message. Cross-Site Request Forgery (CSRF) is an attack that forces an end user to execute unwanted actions on a web application in which they&amp;rsquo;re currently authenticated. CSRF attacks specifically target state-changing requests, not theft of data, since the attacker has no way to see the response to the forged request.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>